Oh, good! Looks a little like a music video shoot.
Hey.
It's good.
Oh, it's growing.
Hello. - Hello.
Okay, today.
We're having a barbecue.
It's summer.
And we're already here.
In the city.
In the middle of Domon
Domonaka
This is Domandakar
Wow!
And there are many ingredients in front of this.
Glad you like it.
Let me introduce you to some of them.
I'm glad.
Saito-san, please.
First of all, onion, lemon and paprika,
Chaz's favorite zucchini.
My favorite grilled chicken.
So cute.
And shrimp.
I love shrimp.
They're the best.
The rest is barbecue and home.
For sure. And a bouchiki.
That's good.
Gutsy. Pork with garlic sauce.
Looks delicious.
G-type.
Looks good.
Gutsy and wrinkled noodles.
Delicious.
It's so delicious. The main meat.
There's a lot of meat.
Oh my god. It looks delicious.
I'm hungry.
Looks so delicious.
Steak.
Steak?
It's really delicious.
It's so delicious.
It's so good.
What's that?
It's like the Grand Canyon.
And the theme of today's barbecue is
We're going to have a barbecue where we're going to bring one story to the table.
You say "one story" a lot.
I heard you have a lot of explaining to do here, too.
Let me explain.
The rule is that each person brings at least one additional item or food item or game to the barbecue that they think would be fun to have.
It's fun. Did everyone bring their own?
I did.
Who brought food?
Yes, I did.
We all brought food. Foodies.
Well, I brought noodles. But these are baked, so to speak, but they're kind of boiled,
What? Is it wrong?
What's wrong with it?
No, seriously, we can just boil them and bake them?
Yes, I want some yakisoba!
I want some yakisoba!
I want it! I want it!
Me?
Yes, I do.
Yes, I think it's good. I'll take care of it.
What? Is this some kind of office worker's lunch?
Office lady's lunch?
What is it?
Ah!
Ha-ha-ha!
Shiri, what are you doing?
Shiitake mushrooms?
Ha-ha-ha!
I smell shiitake mushrooms,
Everyone loves shiitake mushrooms.
Did you bring a lot?
Only 6C.
Oh!
What, what, what?
How many C's?
I'm so sorry.
I'm wearing a lot of clothes.
Only what C?
Me?
Oh, my God!
What? Excuse me.
I'm sorry. I took it on the back porch.
I only brought my 6C.
I'm sorry.
Is that possible?
I just think it's not a good idea.
A girl?
I'm not a girl.
I'm tired.
I'm too weak.
Let's do this once.
Even if we don't finish it, I thought I'd bring it back.
This is so funny.
There's too much, right?
It's too much.
You think it's funny.
I'm so glad.
I can't believe I'm wearing it.
Maybe you should eat shiitake mushrooms.
Shiitake mushrooms have more shiitake mushrooms than meat.
There are lots of flavors, so you can eat shiitake mushrooms with different flavors.
I have shiitake mushrooms, after all.
What is it?
Hamembert.
Ah! Oh, good! It's so good!
Melt it and put something on it.
Shrimp, maybe?
Let's make use of it all.
I can do it!
Marshmallows from
Marshmallows!
Marshmallows on the barbecue, then.
I'm gonna go get some of these mechanical marshmallows.
Yeah, right!
I had to run to three stores.
You didn't find any? I'm looking for these big marshmallows.
Looks so good!
Thank you!
These marshmallows...
Like hasamine cookies.
They are so delicious.
I love them too.
I often eat them at the beauty parlor.
Looks delicious.
With hasamine.
I've been wanting to eat it.
And, you know, I brought one more game.
Hey, Mr. Onji.
May I have a word?
Yes, yes.
This one's for you.
Deco Pin Buster!
Wow!
That's amazing!
It's a game to see how strong the decopin is.
Decopin!
Decopin?
Decopin.
Ha-ha-ha.
Let's do something later to see who's stronger!
Also, I've brought in a story from the Ikoito channel.
Oh, really?
1 kg of beef tongue.
Yay!
It's another river!
That's amazing!
Everyone loves beef tongue, right?
Second place
Yay!
That's great!
Thank you so much!
I can eat so much!
Do you think you can handle it? Because, Mado-san, you have about 1 kg of shiitake mushrooms.
You can eat it, right?
Yes, I can.
Yes, yes.
Then, let's eat it, shall we?
Let's eat.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, I'll go get ready.
Yeah.
What's that?
What's this?
Wait.
It smells so good.
What's that smell?
Green onions.
No green onions?
It smells so good.
Okay, will you do it today?
I'm, uh... I'm, uh..,
I'm a photographer because I'm scared. I'll do my best as a photographer.
Hiyoyo-chan is chopping and dicing the green onions. Cold!
I'm cutting. She is cutting. It's so cute that she's holding the tongs all the time.
Even though we don't grill. Even though we're not burning it. It's hot! Why is that? Oh, paprika is so good.
Paprika.
You've cut bell peppers before?
Oh, my God.
I've cut up bell peppers.
I didn't know they had that many seeds.
I want to look inside.
I'll go.
Smells good.
Sounds good.
Sounds too good.
Smells too good already
And from the real thing in summer.
The finest barbecue barbecue.
Glad it's done, done.
And in such a good color.
Too great.
Pretty gradient.
So beautiful.
You're so good.
It's so beautiful.
Do you always cut hair?
No. Are you the one who cuts hair all the time?
For today.
Hey.
Leeks are good. They're good.
You want to cook? I don't know.
Don't.
What?
No, I don't.
Just a bite.
Oh, yeah.
Take a bite.
Ouch.
Do you want me to do it for you?
Thank you.
I'd like to give it back.
Oh, I'm supposed to give this back? That's a lot.
Give me your hand.
Okay, here we go.
Here you go.
Uhh!
Yeah.
How is it?
Looks good.
It's a big deal.
Is it cooking?
I feel like I'm cooking.
I know.
Yes, it is.
My hands get tired holding this.
It's weak.
I'll go for it.
Here I go.
Oh, wow!
I can stand up so well.
Like this, why are his legs so cool?
His legs are too cool.
Like this, he's fighting.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
I'm going to put it with a big piece of meat.
Is that okay?
Is that how you stab it?
It's kind of like this, isn't it? Look at the side.
It can be anything.
It doesn't matter.
If Cana does it, it's the right thing.
As long as it burns.
There's more.
Shiitake mushroom farmer?
Shiitake mushroom barbecuer.
Wow, I don't think I've ever touched a shiitake before.
Are you kidding me?
First time with raw meat.
How old are you?
Nineteen years.
I might have touched it for 19 years.
Yeah, I just touched it for the first time.
I don't want to do this.
Are you going to be that careful?
You don't wash shiitake mushrooms in water.
They lose their flavor.
Is that so?
Experts?
Do you know anything about mushrooms?
Oh, I don't wash mushrooms.
So I thought I'd just put them on.
Thank you.
Excuse me, shiitake mushrooms and leeks.
Oh, shiitake mushrooms and leeks?
Thank you.
They're huge!
Yes!
It's good, it's good, it's good!
Oh, good!
One is done!
These shiitake mushrooms are so good!
Pretty shiitake mushrooms!
Looks like barbecue!
Barbecue-ish!
I'll cut them together.
Oh, okay, perfect.
Okay!
There you go! It's so cute!
You never know, do you?
The timing.
Finally?
It's possible.
Do I use credit cards?
Oh, credit cards.
I'm sorry, I use cash.
Oh, that's okay.
I'll just use pay-per-view.
PayPay?
Finally!
What's PayPay?
It's all right, then.
I'm going to be a little peculiar.
Please, sir.
Where? Around here?
Right here.
Wait, I think I'm almost done.
Oh, no.
It's not gonna burn.
I don't think it's gonna burn.
It's too uneven.
No, it'll work. If we close this.
If we close it.
Prepare drinks for everyone.
Drinks are out.
What do you want?
Coke.
Coke, sister.
Tea, please.
Yes, please.
The first batch is ready.
Thank you very much.
Okay, Ms. Noguchi.
Yes, I'll make a toast motion here.
We've got it.
I got it.
Please have a drink.
Yes, sir.
Are you hungry?
I am!
Are you ready to eat?
Yes!
Ready, cheers!
Yum!
Cold!
So exciting!
Bon appétit.
Delicious!
Great!
All right! Bon appétit.
Wow!
Yum!
I'll have the ehenghi.
I want to try it with ehenghi butter.
Yes!
It really is!
Shibuya Nakano, I feel like now when I hear it.
Cruise?
Cruise!
This, this?
It smells so good!
Crazy Noguchi?
Yeah!
Oh, no!
I'm Crazy Noguchi.
Will it be Crazy Morojas?
Crazy?
Let's all go crazy!
Let's go crazy!
That's good.
Are we winning?
We're winning?
Congratulations?
I'm serious.
Seven years ago, I couldn't have imagined...
You've lightened up.
Yes, it's gotten brighter.
You're on top of the world.
We're winning.
We're winning. We're winning.
I'm so full of energy.
Are you early?
Yes, it is.
Not yet.
Let's do it now.
Thank you.
No ice!
It went away.
I'm out of ice.
Word Wolf, I want to play Word Wolf.
Let's play Word Wolf.
So, do you want to play Word Wolf?
Yes, I do.
One Wolf?
Yes, sir.
Frank Dravio.
Bon appétit.
Yum!
Yes.
Yum.
Delicious.
Yes. I'll go.
Hey.
I hate.
I hate it too.
I do in Thailand firmly.
Me too.
I can't crush it.
I can do something.
Really?
You can do it with your hands, not with a tissue?
With a net,
Stop it,
And then crush it with a net.
It's a special kind of net.
But, topic #1, have you ever actually encountered this creature? Of course I have.
Yes, I have. I've seen them a lot. Very much so?
Then, topic 2, where do you see it most often? Where do you see it most often?
Oh no! Add that! Is Chutake on? Shootake's on!
Do you see them everywhere? They're in and out.
They're already here. All of a sudden, they're here.
We're all the same. But in Hokkaido, you say you don't see them much.
Yeah, it's like a "Sam-It".
I'll go see him.
Odai-san, who do you dislike the most in this group?
Cure Rho.
I got it.
Doubtful.
And I got it.
I know who the douche is, and I know what he's talking about.
No, no, no, no, no.
I don't know anything.
I, on the contrary.
I think Cure Rho and I are probably buddies.
Oh, you're buddies?
I thought we were buddies.
I thought we were buddies, too.
You're alone.
How much time do we have?
One minute.
What do you think, Haru?
I think four minutes.
Four minutes.
I'm with Yori. I'm with Yori? I think so. And I know what kind of creature she is.
I'm not talking. I don't have any information. What's it look like?
What color is it? Black.
One color?
Scary eyes. One color?
Scary. One color?
One color? One color?
What color is black? How big?
This one?
What? Toward?
Toward? Toward?
Towards? Towards?
Scary. It's pretty big, isn't it?
Scary.
This one?
Can you touch it? With your bare hands.
No, I can't touch it.
Some people might.
I've been thinking about what you said yesterday.
You said you could crush it with your hands.
I don't have an image of people who crush things with their hands.
I don't. Is that so?
But it's like a special net.
A net?
I don't have that image either.
Then it's a net!
A net.
We'll do it with a net.
Freeze it!
Freeze it?
Freeze!
Freeze it, you say.
And you take it out with a net?
Have you done that twice?
With a net?
With a big one, bam!
And then, jeez!
But..,
I've never had it happen at my house.
What?
I don't know any more.
I've never been in any of the houses I've lived in, or moved to.
I've never left any of them, not even in the summer.
Really?
You said you were going to crush Hana-chan...
Wow, a container of oil.
Like you can crush it? You can't.
She'll never crush it.
I'll go with you.
I'll go with you then.
Okay, I'm in.
Okay.
I'll crush you.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh no!
Sana, Sana, Sana, Sana, Kihara.
Here we go.
Who's the Wolf?
Sana-chan.
Definitely everyone.
They're all looking at us.
I thought Chiara was one of them,
But when I talked to her, I felt differently,
I thought it's like they don't appear in Hokkaido.
Then it's a cockroach.
Wait, so you thought I was Taft,
I had to get in, so I did.
So, you got caught out of the blue?
Did they know you were doing it?
I'm riding on a cockroach.
Because it says "net" on it.
It says "net.
It says "net".
I'm Three Days and you're Tufts.
No, it's not.
What's too unique about it?
It's like they don't exist in Hokkaido.
So where was it?
Like Sumikawa.
More and more.
You're not very good at this.
I got out all right.
Okay, the comb is ready.
It's done.
Looks like an Amen-type comb.
You look great.
I look pretty.
Bon appétit.
Your mouth is waking up.
Mmm.
Yum!
Hikitake mushrooms are delicious.
Delicious!
Delicious bamboo shoots!
This is!
Thank you so much for the delicious mushrooms!
We have more!
I have about 7 packs of shiitake mushrooms!
This one is kind of hard...
He says, "Hey, it's not noisy, hey, it's not noisy, hey, it's not noisy.
Come on, you, get out of here!
Not too loud, not too loud...
I'm playing bug cuties.
Go to sleep.
Go to sleep, go to sleep.
Nara-na-na-na-na.
Come on.
Okay, I'm going.
Yes.
So, here is this week's treasure of the week.
Whoever has the slowest pace in this game gets to make yakisoba.
Yay!
It's going to be a taste of many different families.
That's right. And for yakisoba, too.
Let's have them cook it.
It's a one-shot deal, right?
Yes, it's good.
It's good!
It's good to ignore pressure, isn't it?
I believe in it. I do.
Is this low?
171.
Is that low?
It's a little weak, isn't it?
It's low.
Okay, bye.
That's me! I've never done this before.
Here we go. Ready.
No, even if it's an error.
Hold it down.
Here we go. Ready.
Oh, no, no, no. I'm sorry.
Here we go. Let's go.
It's 3.0.
0?
Isn't this an error?
Zero.
Is this possible?
Yes. Then it's 0.
I still don't know.
I don't know yet.
It could be that I'm leaving.
Zero?
I'll let you go.
You seem stronger than this.
I'm weak.
Like this.
Let's do it.
Oh, no.
No. 1.
Five.
Yes.
Zero.
Seino
Wow, gorilla.
What?
Forty-five.
how do you do that?
I mean...
Let's see.
I mean, 1234th.
I made it nicely.
Yay!
Grover is something really serious once.
Give me one.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, shit!
Ah!
That's 171.
Oh, my God.
Well, well, well, well.
What is this?
I don't know why I saw zero first like that, but I got zero. Let's get some yakisoba for the cancher and some Asian hair cuckolding for the dog Caralee.
Cackling Cackling
I'll do my best
I'll do my best.
Oh, man...
Here you go.
Once it's all in...
I'll put it all in.
I'll put it in.
I'm gonna put it in.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait. Maybe half is just fine.
Wait.
Yakisoba
Noodles Noodles Noodles Noodles
It's too early.
Too early.
Which way is too much?
O-la-la-la-la-la-la...
All right.
Wow, that's good. It's true, the charred onion is necessary for yakisoba, isn't it?
Oh, it's good. It's good.
It's amazing. It looks like a monjiya. The waiter always does this for me.
May I?
This is a can again.
Chururi chururi.
Delicious!
All right!
Cut this off with a thud.
Ooh!
All right! Here we go!
Noodles in!
Oh, no! Wow!
Wow!
It's so thick!
Looks so good! Those noodles! Thick noodles!
I've never cooked yakisoba before.
It's like this.
I've only made ramen noodles before.
When I made ramen, it took me an hour and there was no soup.
It's really puffy!
I've made my family eat ramen noodles this thick
I've made it so thick that my family ate it and made it airy.
Sounds great!
Making yakisoba might be fun!
Thank you for watching!
Pork Garlic Sauce
Very thick sauce...
Sounds good. - Sounds good.
So much garlic!
Looks delicious, guys.
Oh, yeah, it's so good.
I love yakisoba noodles. I forgot I love yakisoba noodles.
I love yakisoba. I just remembered.
I just remembered I love yakisoba.
I love thick yakisoba.
Okay, everyone, yakisoba is ready!
Looks so good!
It was even better than that.
It smells so good.
What kind of yakisoba is this?
It sure does!
Um, this is shrimp puri-puri yakisoba.
You did it!
Looks so delicious!
Puri-Puri Spicy Yakisoba
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Oh, no, no, no!
It's good, it's good, it's good.
A little too spicy?
It's good, right?
It's good.
It's so perfect.
I'm so happy.
Looks delicious.
Thank you so much.
For making it.
I'm glad you made it.
I'm glad you could make it.
I really wanted to eat yakisoba.
I can make yakisoba from now on.
I can make yakisoba now.
It smells so good.
Riding on the wind.
Bon appétit.
Thank you. I'll take it.
Thank you. Gia ratchetian.
Bon appétit.
Looks delicious.
Oh, no!
It's delicious.
It's really good.
It's very popular.
Maybe it's famous.
It's delicious.
This is amazing.
He's a genius.
He's a winner.
It's genius.
I'm not a breakfast person, but this place makes me want to eat breakfast.
Maybe a little.
Here he comes.
What?
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Um, happy.
You're the best.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Nice summer
I kinda want to go to the pool
I know what you mean. I want to eat bonito in the ocean.
Wow, that's nice. Like a beach house.
A beach house.
The ocean of the ocean.
Sea squids
Miss, miss, miss.
It's a girl. A fish in the sea
I knew it! It's so hard!
Please bake the mash
I'm asking about the location
surface
Mi uka stell
moooooood like a glutinous rice cake with time wowirlo lings
Yummmmmm
I'll put it here.
Cute...
It's a rice cake
No, it's not.
Será que es suficiente.
Help me, alas!
Delicious today.
I can take it to the store!
Is it on?
I'm here. I'll be there.
So, they made dessert. My recommendation.
Thank you.
Okay. Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
Yay!
It's good.
It was delicious.
It was like I ate myself out.
I cried.
May I?
Yeah.
Wow. Wow. Wow.
What's right?
It's true.
Hooky code.
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
Oh, wow.
Oh, no.
It's totally coming. All of it.
It's all coming.
Oh, that's good. It's good.
Isn't it good?
Sticky. It's good. It's good.
Sweet. It's good.
It's delicious. Very tasty.
It's delicious.
What's the aroma?
I feel like it has a gentle taste.
It's super delicious.
No, it's not.
It's sticky.
It's a snow apple. Amazing.
You can do anything.
So, would you like baked sesame seeds?
Baked sesame seeds.
Like this.
Like this, like this.
Koukoukou koukou koukou koukou koukou.
Wow, absolutely.
Josie so awesome and delicious Цзلا
look they are programming
P consequens
Ah gen
Seriously.
Delicious!
Don't eat it.
Who brought the ring?
I did.
The singer tastes like grilled arancotti.
What? I'm scared.
It's sticky.
But I think I know what it tastes like.
It tastes like my house.
I don't know.
Eat it. Can you eat an apple?
It tastes like Ikehara's parents'.
It tastes like my parents' house.
You know what I mean?
At my house...
You can have a taste of the Ikehara family.
I'll take it.
It's just like my parents'.
Hana-chan's family?
I might have mixed them up. I cut it myself.
Oh! That's what I meant.
Delusion.
So, that's it.
Jill.
It was delicious.
Everyone's individual gifts were put to good use,
It was a lot of fun.
Let's enjoy the summer a lot more.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.